koalaquiz.net 2017-12-19

# Koala Quiz

### Introduction

Before the New Development of communication tools, It Is Necessary porter A Special attention to the protection of private life . That's Why We undertake one respect the confidentiality of Personal Information we collect What .

* * *

### Collection of Personal Information

We collect the following information:

  * Name
  * First name
  * Email address
  * Gender / Sex
  * Age / Date of Birth
  * Facebook informations collected
  * email : Provides access to the person's primary email address. 
  * public_profile : Provides access to a person's basic information, including first name, last name, profile picture, gender and age range.
  * user_birthday : Provides access to a person's birth date, including the day, year and month. 
  * user_friends : Provides access to a person's list of friends that also use your app. 
  * user_likes : Provides access to the list of all pages and Open Graph objects that a person has liked. 
  * user_photos : Provides access to photos a person has uploaded or been tagged in. 
  * user_posts : Provides access to the posts on a person's Timeline, including their own posts and posts from others.

The personal information we collect is collected through forms and through the interactivity between you and our website . We also use, as indicated in the following section, cookies and / or log files to collect information about you.

* * *

### Forms and interactivity :

Your personal information is collected through forms , namely:

  * Registration Form website

We use the information thus collected for the following purposes:

  * Information / Promotional offers
  * Statistics

Your information is also collected through the interactivity that can be established between you and our website with this , as follows :

We use the information thus collected for the following purposes:

* * *

### Log files and cookies

We collect certain information through log files (log file) and cookies (cookies) . These are mainly the following information:

  * IP address
  * Operating system
  * Pages visited and queries
  * Time and day of connection

The use of such files allows us:

  * Improved service and personalized welcome
  * Consumer Custom Profile
  * Statistic

* * *

### Right of opposition and withdrawal

We are committed to providing you with right of objection and withdrawal regarding your personal information.

The right of veto is defined as the possibility offered to users to refuse that their personal information used for certain purposes mentioned in the collection.   

The right of withdrawal is defined as the possibility offered to users to request that their personal information no longer included , for example, in a mailing list.

To exercise these rights, you can :

Email: info@koalaquiz.net

* * *

### Access permission

We are committed to recognizing the right of access and rectification to data subjects wishing to access, modify or even write off information about them.

The exercise of this right will be :

Email : info@koalaquiz.net

* * *

### Security

The personal information we collect is kept in a secure environment . People working for us are obliged to respect the confidentiality of your information.

To ensure the security of your personal information , we use the following measures : 

  * Access management - authorized person
  * Access management - person
  * Login / password

We are committed to maintaining a high degree of confidentiality by integrating the latest technological innovations to ensure the confidentiality of your transactions. However, since no mechanism offers maximum security, risk is always present when the Internet is used to transmit personal information. 

The entire KoalaQuiz team (Koala included) works hard every day to amuse surprise and entertain you. You have a smile enjoying a nice moment on the site? Mission accomplished!

KoalaQuiz offers you tests to better know yourself: your temper, your personality, your values, your take on life… that’s right: it’s all about YOU. There are also more amusing ones, to know, for example, what your fortune cookie is or which animal you are.

An interesting result entertains and surprises you? Share this little moment of happiness with family and friends: happiness is the only thing that multiplies when shared after all!

Take a seat, relax, grab some eucalyptus leaves (maybe) and try your first test! Enjoy!
